Every step counts.
Happy Feet Two is a animation, comedy, family film directed by George Miller.
Mumble the penguin has a problem: his son Erik, who is reluctant to
dance, encounters the Mighty Sven — a penguin who can fly!
Things get worse for Mumble when the world is shaken by powerful forces, causing him to
bring together the penguin nations and their allies to set things right.
Mumble (voice), played by Elijah Wood.
Ramon / Lovelace (voice), played by Robin Williams.
Gloria (voice), played by P!nk.
Erik (voice), played by E. G. Daily.
Lombardo (voice), played by Johnny A. Sanchez.
Raul (voice), played by Lombardo Boyar.
Happy Feet Two is a 2011 animated jukebox musical comedy
film directed and co-written by George Miller.
It is the sequel to the 2006 film Happy Feet.
Elijah Wood, Robin Williams, Hugo Weaving, Magda Szubanski and Anthony LaPaglia reprise their roles from the first film,
with Common, P!nk, Hank Azaria, Brad Pitt, Matt Damon, Sofia Vergara, and Richard Carter joining the cast.
In the film, young penguin Erik, the son of Mumble and Gloria, who is reluctant to
dance, runs away from home and encounters the Mighty Sven, a tufted puffin.
When the penguins are trapped by a giant wall of ice
and snow, they must save Antarctica.
An international co-production between the United States and Australia, Happy Feet Two was released
in North American theaters on November 18, 2011, and in Australia on December 26.
The film received mixed reviews, and underperformed at the box office,
grossing $159 million against its $135 million budget.
This resulted in the closure of Miller's Dr.
D Studios, making this their only animated film.
The film explores themes of penguin, musical,
aftercreditsstinger, inspirational.
The tone is lighthearted.